[EP13]
I'll save her.
You don't deserve to be a doctor.
It's you who killed my family.
[I can't let fear]
[stop me from saving lives.]
Wanwan,
I've got the car ready.
In five minutes,
take Second Aunt
and leave through the back door.
She won't make it to the hospital.
Even if she does,
with the current medical equipment,
she won't survive.
Go pack your clothes.
Do you trust me?
I do.
But you know Grandma.
With her temper,
she won't do anything
to me,
But for you...
I'm your wife,
and the Ling family's wife.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here for you.
Do what you want to do.
This is the scent on Zhaoyue.
Could it be that the Second Madame killed Zhaoyue?
But I have no evidence.
There are thousands of perfumes in the world.
What if it's just a coincidence?
Better to kill a thousand by mistake
than let one slip away.
What if it really is the Second Concubine?
Medical conditions in the Republic of China were poor.
It's common for two lives to be in one body.
Save me.
Save my child.
I can't let anyone die in front of me.
She's given birth.
Really?
A boy
or
a girl?
A boy.
Second Madame and the baby are fine.
I'll prescribe some tonic medicine.
She'll be cured after a few days of recuperation.
But
the baby was born
with cyanotic lips.
I'm afraid he has asthma.
This disease
is most afraid of noise and fatigue.
It's best to lie down and rest often.
Avoid
getting angry, overexertion, and excessive exercise.
As long as you are willing to put this medicine
into your master's food,
not only will this money be yours,
but I will also give you a large sum of money later.
Think about your sick mother without money for treatment.
I don't need to tell you what to do, right?
Young Madam, don't blame me for being cruel.
Brother,
why are you here?
Don't move.
Your poison has not been detoxified.
I've been very careful.
The maids are all from the Su family.
Could it be
they have bribed the maids from the Su family?
Young Madam,
here are some snacks from the kitchen.
Give them to me.
The Sus are not what they used to be.
It's normal for me to be disloyal.
Although the poison hasn't been detoxified,
it won't be life-threatening.
I'm going to leave Yang City for a while
to find the antidote.
Be careful.
Brother, stop talking about me.
How are you doing?
Did you find anything?
Any progress recently?
Mother and Moon often go to
the orphanage
besides the Su's business.
I've been to the orphanage to investigate,
but the children there cried when they saw me.
I couldn't get any information.
Forget it. I'll go to the orphanage tomorrow.
I've heard Deputy Li say that
the little stable boy
who accidentally broke into the team
on the day when the Marshal got killed
was from this orphanage.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm Su Muwan, the daughter of the Su family.
You're Mrs. Ling,
the wife of the Young Marshal.
You're so pretty.
Young Madam, we are all orphans who have escaped from the war.
We were refused by other places.
It's the Marshal and the Young Marshal
who gave us such a beautiful house.
You can tell me whatever you want to eat.
I'll buy it for you.
- Great. - Great.
Great.
Nanfeng, tell me whatever you want.
I'll buy it for you.
Really? That's great!
Young Master,
we've cut off all herbal medicine sales,
leaving only Hongji Hall.
You mentioned burning down this orphanage.
Orphanage?
Leave it be.
By the way,
do you know a child named
Abao?
Abao...
He...
What happened to him?
He got into a car accident.
He's still in a coma.
How did this happen all of a sudden?
No,
I have to go see him.
This way,
he's right there.
The doctor said Abao might wake up tomorrow,
or never.
[The car accident is so strange.]
[It seems to be related to the death of the Old Marshal.]
[Did she see something?]
[She's just a stable boy.]
[How could she have such a delicate handkerchief?]
[Could it be left by the murderer by accident?]
[This handkerchief is very distinctive.]
[It can't be owned by ordinary people.]
[Chu Nanfeng is surrounded by women all year round.]
[Maybe]
he knows who the owner is.
Last time it was because of Ling Shenxing.
What's the reason this time?
Xiao Wan,
can't you just ask me out because you want to see me?
When I have something,
you're the first one I think of.
Isn't that enough?
But I never do anything for nothing,
and I don't want you to see me because of someone else.
Then let's stick to the old rules.
I'll give you my time.
Please.